moreystudio.com 2003-12-08

# Morey Studio - Public Gallery Entrance

**_Morey Studio Privacy Policy_**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice  
explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the MoreyStudio.com website

_The Information We Collect:_

When you sign up for membership in the Private Archive, your email address is entered into our database so that we may keep in contact with you regarding special offers and updates to the site and news that may be of interest to members. No other information is collected at that time. (Please see our payment processor's Privacy Policy concerning their collected information).

On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, or register to receive materials. The type of personal information collected on these pages is primarily email addresses; however, you may also be asked to give a billing or shipping address, credit card information, etc. This information is used solely to complete the request or transaction you're involved in at that time and it is not retained for any other use. 

_The Way We Use Information:_

Information requested to complete a purchase or other type of transaction is used only for that limited purpose and is not maintained for other uses. Your personal information is not stored on line and is never sold or transferred to other parties.

We send out update information about this site approx three or four times monthly to all email addresses in our databank. If you do not wish to receive email from this site, you may remove yourself from the list of recipients by sending a request to info@moreystudio.com, with the word "remove" in the subject heading.

_Our Commitment To Data Security_

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

_How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:_

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending a request to info@moreystudio.com. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

_How To Contact Us:_

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us by email at info@moreystudio.com
